Adam Hoff

Full-stack Web Developer

(571) 439-9011 | adamhoff79@gmail.com | Northern Virginia/Metro D.C. Area

My Portfolio

http://adamhoff.github.io/portfolio

Front-end portfolio website utilizing HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that contains other web development projects that I created during my time at General Assembly.

Profile

I am a Junior full-stack web developer with a passion for all things technology. I have a strong desire to learn, and a notable attention to detail. My ability to solve problems under pressure makes me an asset for any individual or team oriented work environment. I am a quick learner who grasps new skills and ideas without hesitation. My enthusiasm for the field has driven me to use the best practices throughout all of my work.

Technical Skills

HTML5	CSS	JavaScript	jQuery	
React	Ruby on Rails	AngularJS	Meteor	
Bootstrap	Express	MongoDB	Java	

Areas of Expertise

Front-end development	Ι	Agile programming	T	Object oriented programming
Front-end design	Ι	Git workflows	Ι	Team collaborating

Experience

WEB DEVELOPER STUDENT, GENERAL ASSEMBLY D.C.

MAR 2017-JUN 2017

A 12 week, 10 hour a day web development bootcamp where I learned programming fundamentals, product development, front and back-end web development, and how to collaborate with a team of developers to create a finished product. During this time I created my portfolio website which houses links and information to other projects I completed during my time at General Assembly.

LIFEGUARD, FRANKLIN PARK POOL

MAY 2012-SEP 2016

Red Cross CPR and First Aid trained and certified. Helped teach new employees how to handle emergency situations at our facility; ensured compliance with established rules and guidelines by both employees and patrons; assisted with pool maintenance. Through the performance of numerous rescues while on duty, I learned how to perform well under stress and pressure.

LIFEGUARD, STONELEIGH GOLF & COUNTRY CLUB

MAY 2014-AUG 2015

Red Cross CPR and First Aid trained and certified. helped maintain constant surveillance of patrons within the facility; ensured compliance with established rules and guidelines by patrons; assisted with pool maintenance.

Education

General Assembly; Web Development Immersive, Washington D.C.

MAR 2017-JUNE 2017

University of Mary Washington, Fredericksburg VA

AUG 2014-DEC 2016